

Profile

My work experience inside a company is mostly in **testing and requirement writing/validation** but in the last period of time, I've started learning Web Development and starting playing around with Java/Python. I am trying to find a path and start to specialize in the development of applications and I think this can be a good opportunity for me to start my path.

Employment History

Data entry specialist, Orca Book Storage, Poole, United Kingdom

JULY 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

- -organize book storage
- -add new entries
- -prepare orders for customers(small for personal use or big for companies)

Software Tester, Continental, Iasi, Romania

OCTOBER 2018 - JULY 2019

- -create test cases to verify specific requirements
- -create automatic test cases
- -continuous-integration testing
- -manual testing
- -tested new software builds and performed troubleshooting on existing software applications.
- -functionality testing and regression testing

PDE(Pilot developement electronique), Renault, Bucuresti, Romania

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2018

Renault Romania, Bucuresti (Romania)

- -worked on radio10, TCU(Connectivity) and Multimedia(ULC-navigation)
- -development of certain parts of an electronic device
- -add specification or change them
- -discussions with suppliers regarding the new software, hardware or configuration/calibration for the new piece in different fabrics over the world
- -validation static or dynamic
- -management of the TCU

Consultant(Technical Referent), Alten, Iasi, Romania

NOVEMBER 2015 - AUGUST 2017

-Update/Create test plans/test cases for PSA PEUGEOT CITROEN regarding the functionality/defects

or performance of certain functions. (Example: Interior Lighting/Exterior Lighting/Clock/NightVision/Maintenance...)

- -Analyze the difference between requirements and create a plan for the new update.
- -Discuss with the client and present to him the update or the corrections that are needed.
- -Help and tutor new colleagues, give them different advice or correcting their work(filling check-lists and explain them the errors).
- -Assisting the seniors in creating different tutorials/calculating RFT or OTD, intern files and so on...

Details

lasi, Romania 0745191817

baciudanielmarian@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Romanian

DRIVING LICENSE

В

Skills

HTML5

CSS

Java

Python Agile

JavaScript

Android Development

Languages

English

French

Hobbies

Chess, Guitar

Education

Bachelor(unfinished-last exam in July), Faculty of Automatic and Computer Engineering Iasi, Iasi

OCTOBER 2011 - JULY 2015

Mathematical Informatics, Nicolae Iorga, Negresti, Negresti

APRIL 2020 - APRIL 2020

HTML Essential Training, LinkedIn online

AUGUST 2015

References

Courses

Introduction to HTML, Coursera

MARCH 2020

Javascript Essential training, LinkedIn

APRIL 2020 - APRIL 2020

APRIL 2017

Digital Marketing, Atelierul Digital(Google)

2016

Extra-curricular activities

APRIL 2020 - APRIL 2020